<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Wolf Den</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Wolf Den</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 23:05:59 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB Blunder</title>
      <link>/posts/blunder_writeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 23:05:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blunder_writeup/</guid>
      <description>Blunder is a box that starts with a Bludit based blog being used to store random facts and a Sudoers file was configured with the intent to prevent us from running bash as root. It was less than sucessful.
Scanning and Enumeration We start off with a basic nmap scan.
sudo nmap -sV -sC 10.10.10.191 Starting Nmap 7.80 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2020-06-21 08:44 MDT Nmap scan report for 10.10.10.191 Host is up (0.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB Admirer</title>
      <link>/posts/admirer_writeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 17:44:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/admirer_writeup/</guid>
      <description>Admirer Admirer is a Linux box that features a vulnerable database setup and leveraging a maliciously crafted python library to achieve root.
Enumeration We start off, as always, with an NMAP Scan.
Nmap scan report for 10.10.10.187Host is up (0.12s latency).Not shown: 997 closed portsPORT STATE SERVICE VERSION21/tcp open ftp vsftpd 3.0.322/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 7.4p1 Debian 10+deb9u7 (protocol 2.0)| ssh-hostkey:| 2048 4a:71:e9:21:63:69:9d:cb:dd:84:02:1a:23:97:e1:b9 (RSA)| 256 c5:95:b6:21:4d:46:a4:25:55:7a:87:3e:19:a8:e7:02 (ECDSA)|_ 256 d0:2d:dd:d0:5c:42:f8:7b:31:5a:be:57:c4:a9:a7:56 (ED25519)80/tcp open http Apache httpd 2.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UIUCTF Kernel_Memory_Leak</title>
      <link>/posts/kernelaslr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 17:44:50 -0602</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/kernelaslr/</guid>
      <description>Kernel_Memory_Leak The kernel is leaking memory to the user! That&#39;s probably not good, right?One of the syscalls can be convinced to leak the kernel stack. Find the leak and you&#39;ll receive a flag. Keep leaking kernel secrets until you see the }.(Hint: finding the leak is half the battle, getting it to leak the entire flag requires some outside the box thinking)Author: raviDisclaimer I was unable to solve this challenge until after the CTF had officially ended.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UIUCTF Whats_A_Syscall</title>
      <link>/posts/whats_a_syscall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 17:44:50 -0601</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/whats_a_syscall/</guid>
      <description>Whats_A_Syscall? Challenge Description
Syscall 14 is known as &amp;quot;SANDBOX_SPECIAL&amp;quot;... I wonder if that would be useful here.You&#39;ll be stuck in a never ending loop of binexec until you perform syscall 14.To learn about syscalls and how they work in pwnyOS, check out the documentation!System Calls in pwnyOS: https://github.com/sigpwny/pwnyOS-2020-docs/blob/master/Syscalls.pdfAuthor: raviSolution We start out with a welcome screen and are told that we are in a sandbox.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UIUCTF Time_To_Start</title>
      <link>/posts/time_to_start/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 17:44:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/time_to_start/</guid>
      <description>Time_To_Start Challenge Description
Welcome to pwnyOS!!pwnyOS is a custom x86 operating system that supports link-time kASLR, multitasking and kernel threads, execution of genuine ELF files, a realtime high resolution graphics engine, and a custom hierarchical file system. This OS was written from the ground up with its use as a challenge for UIUCTF 2020 in mind. All source code in the OS is 100% custom handwritten C and assembly- there are no libraries used, and none of its code can be found anywhere online.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB Tabby</title>
      <link>/posts/tabby_writeup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/tabby_writeup/</guid>
      <description>Tabby has a Tomcat server that doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to have vulnerability we can exploit. But we chaining an LFI allows us to make use of it. Containers also prove to be useful for more than what they were intended for.
Scanning and enumeration We start off, as always, with an NMAP scan to get an idea of what we are working with.
nightwolf@kali:~/CTFs/HTB/Tabby$ nmap -sV -sC 10.10.10.194 Starting Nmap 7.80 ( https://nmap.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
